{
  "zamtrios": {
    "name": "Zamtrios",
    "locations": [
      {
        "location": "Loloska",
        "postGame": false
      }
    ],
    "pattern": "amphibian",
    "rank": "low",
    "back": "cyan",
    "front": "orange"
  },
  "blueYianKutKu": {
    "name": "Blue Yian Kut-Ku",
    "locations": [
      {
        "location": "Alcala",
        "postGame": false
      }
    ],
    "pattern": "birdWyvern",
    "rank": "low",
    "back": "mintGreen",
    "front": "yellow"
  },
  "crimsonQurupeco": {
    "name": "Crimson Qurupeco",
    "locations": [
      {
        "location": "Pomore Garden",
        "postGame": false
      }
    ],
    "pattern": "birdWyvern",
    "rank": "low",
    "back": "red",
    "front": "yellow"
  },
  "gendrome": {
    "name": "Gendrome",
    "locations": [
      {
        "location": "Lamure (Desert)",
        "postGame": false
      }
    ],
    "pattern": "birdWyvern",
    "rank": "low",
    "back": "limeGreen",
    "front": "lightOrange"
  },
  "greatBaggi": {
    "name": "Great Baggi",
    "locations": [
      {
        "location": "Loloska",
        "postGame": false
      }
    ],
    "pattern": "birdWyvern",
    "rank": "low",
    "back": "blue",
    "front": "yellow"
  },

  "greatJaggi":{"name":"Great Jaggi","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"purple","front":"red"},
  "gypceros":{"name":"Gypceros","locations":[],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"lightBlue","front":"fuchsia"},
  "iodrome":{"name":"Iodrome","locations":[],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"red","front":"darkPurple"},
  "kulaYaKu":{"name":"Kula Ya-Ku","locations":[],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"orange"},
  "pukeiPukei":{"name":"Pukei-Pukei","locations":[],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkGreen","front":"tan"},
  "purpleGypceros":{"name":"Purple Gypceros","locations":[],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkPurple","front":"green"},
  "qurupeco":{"name":"Qurupeco","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"lightGreen","front":"lightPurple"},
  "velocidrome":{"name":"Velocidrome","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":false}],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"lightBlue","front":"orange"},
  "yianGaruga":{"name":"Yian Garuga","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkBlue","front":"pink"},
  "yianKutKu":{"name":"Yian Kut-Ku","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":false}],"pattern":"birdWyvern","rank":"low","back":"pink","front":"blue"},

  "anjanath":{"name":"Anjanath","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"pink","front":"black"},
  "barroth":{"name":"Barroth","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"reddishBrown","front":"orange"},
  "brachydios":{"name":"Brachydios","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"blue","front":"limeGreen"},
  "deviljho":{"name":"Deviljho","locations":[{"location":"All","postGame":true}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"green","front":"red"},
  "fulgurAnjanath":{"name":"Fulgur Anjanath","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":true}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"red"},
  "glavenus":{"name":"Glavenus","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":true},{"location":"Terga","postGame":true}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkBlue","front":"red"},
  "jadeBarroth":{"name":"Jade Barroth","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"cyan","front":"teal"},
  "uragaan":{"name":"Uragaan","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"bruteWyvern","rank":"low","back":"yellow","front":"crimson"},

  "arzuros":{"name":"Arzuros","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"blue","front":"green"},
  "ashKechaWacha":{"name":"Ash Kecha Wacha","locations":[{"location":"Lamure (Tower)","postGame":false},{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"orange"},
  "bulldrome":{"name":"Bulldrome","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"brown","front":"tan"},
  "congalala":{"name":"Congalala","locations":[{"location":"Loloska (Woodlands)","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"brightPink","front":"limeGreen"},
  "emeraldCongalala":{"name":"Emerald Congalala","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"limeGreen","front":"lightOrange"},
  "gammoth":{"name":"Gammoth","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"darkBlue","front":"crimson"},
  "kechaWacha":{"name":"Kecha Wacha","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"lightOrange","front":"red"},
  "lagombi":{"name":"Lagombi","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedBeast","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"darkPurple"},

  "stygianZinogre":{"name":"Stygian Zinogre","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"fangedWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkBlue","front":"tan"},
  "tobiKadachi":{"name":"Tobi Kadachi","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"black"},
  "zinogre":{"name":"Zinogre","locations":[{"location":"Lamure (Royal Monster)","postGame":false},{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"fangedWyvern","rank":"low","back":"teal","front":"yellow"},

  "astalos":{"name":"Astalos","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"black","front":"lightGreen"},
  "azureRathalos":{"name":"Azure Rathalos","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"lightBlue","front":"darkCyan"},
  "barioth":{"name":"Barioth","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"orange"},
  "basarios":{"name":"Basarios","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"lightBrown"},
  "bazelgeuse":{"name":"Bazelgeuse","locations":[{"location":"All","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"black"},
  "bruteTigrex":{"name":"Brute Tigrex","locations":[{"location":"All","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"olive","front":"lightOrange"},
  "blackDiablos":{"name":"Black Diablos","locations":[{"location":"Lamure","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"olive","front":"grey"},
  "blackGravios":{"name":"Black Gravios","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"red","front":"grey"},
  "diablos":{"name":"Diablos","locations":[{"location":"Lamure","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"lightOrange"},
  "gravios":{"name":"Gravios","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"lightOrange"},
  "greenNargacuga":{"name":"Green Nargacuga","locations":[{"location":"Pomore Garden","postGame":false},{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"limeGreen","front":"yellow"},
  "khezu":{"name":"Khezu","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"fuchsia"},
  "legiana":{"name":"Legiana","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"black"},
  "monoblos":{"name":"Monoblos","locations":[{"location":"Alcala (Royal Monster)","postGame":false},{"location":"Lamure","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"orange","front":"red"},
  "nargacuga":{"name":"Nargacuga","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"darkBlue","front":"fuchsia"},
  "paolumu":{"name":"Paolumu","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"peach"},
  "pinkRathian":{"name":"Pink Rathian","locations":[{"location":"Pomore Garden","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"peach","front":"red"},
  "rathalos":{"name":"Rathalos","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"red","front":"darkBlue"},
  "rathian":{"name":"Rathian","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"limeGreen"},
  "redKhezu":{"name":"Red Khezu","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"red","front":"peach"},
  "rubyBasarios":{"name":"Ruby Basarios","locations":[{"location":"Pomore Garden","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"limeGreen","front":"fuchsia"},
  "sandBarioth":{"name":"Sand Barioth","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"orange","front":"red"},
  "seregios":{"name":"Seregios","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"yellow","front":"red"},
  "tigrex":{"name":"Tigrex","locations":[{"location":"Lamure","postGame":false}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"lightOrange","front":"blue"},
  "whiteMonoblos":{"name":"White Monoblos","locations":[{"location":"Lamure (Royal Monster)","postGame":false},{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":true}],"pattern":"flyingWyvern","rank":"low","back":"tan","front":"grey"},
  
  "apceros":{"name":"Apceros","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"herbivore","rank":"low","back":"orange","front":"tan"},
  "aptonoth":{"name":"Aptonoth","locations":[{"location":"Hakolo","postGame":false}],"pattern":"herbivore","rank":"low","back":"darkGreen","front":"olive"},
  "popo":{"name":"Popo","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"herbivore","rank":"low","back":"reddishBrown","front":"yellow"},

  "ivoryLagiacrus":{"name":"Ivory Lagiacrus","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"leviathan","rank":"low","back":"blue","front":"yellow"},
  "lagiacrus":{"name":"Lagiacrus","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"leviathan","rank":"low","back":"lightBlue","front":"red"},
  "mitzutsune":{"name":"Mitzutsune","locations":[{"location":"Pomore Garden","postGame":false}],"pattern":"leviathan","rank":"low","back":"red","front":"tan"}  ,
  "purpleLudroth":{"name":"Purple Ludroth","locations":[{"location":"Lamure","postGame":false}],"pattern":"leviathan","rank":"low","back":"fuchsia","front":"palePurple"},
  "royalLudroth":{"name":"Royal Ludroth","locations":[{"location":"Alcala","postGame":false}],"pattern":"leviathan","rank":"low","back":"limeGreen","front":"yellow"},

  "cephadrome":{"name":"Cephadrome","locations":[{"location":"Lamure (Desert)","postGame":false}],"pattern":"piscineWyvern","rank":"low","back":"olive","front":"red"},

  "nerscylla":{"name":"Nerscylla","locations":[{"location":"Loloska","postGame":false}],"pattern":"temnoceran","rank":"low","back":"lightPurple","front":"red"},
  "shroudedNerscylla":{"name":"Shrouded Nerscylla","locations":[{"location":"Terga","postGame":false}],"pattern":"temnoceran","rank":"low","back":"white","front":"yellow"}
}